Warren Mitofsky Papers 2008.0071
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Elections, 1948-2006
  - Subseries B: Midterm Elections
    - 1990
      - Election Overview (Box 7)
      - Exit Poll Materials (Box 7)
      - General Election (Box 7)
      - Illinois Primary (Box 7)
      - National Front General Election (Box 7)
      - Primary – Chicago (Box 7)
      - Third Party Letters of Complaint (Box 7)
      - Turnout Calculations (Box 7)
      - Voting and Registration in the Election of November 1990 (Box 7)
      - VRS – Exit Poll Bids (Box 7)
    - 1994
      - ENS General Election (Box 7)
      - Exit Polls Final Andy’s Que (Box 7)
      - Final Tabs (3 folders) (Box 7)
      - Michigan Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - Arizona Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - California Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - Connecticut Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - Florida Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - Maryland Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - Massachusetts Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - New York Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - Pennsylvania Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - Tennessee Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - Texas Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - Virginia Governor Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - New Jersey Senate Horizontal Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - Jewish Vote (Box 7)
      - National Exit Poll (Box 7)
      - National Exit Poll – Females (Box 7)
      - National Exit Poll Horizontal (Box 7)
      - National Exit Poll - Midwest (Box 7)
      - National Exit Poll – Males (Box 7)
      - National Exit Poll – Northeast (Box 7)
      - National Exit Poll - South (Box 7)
      - National Exit Poll – West (Box 7)
      - National Exit Poll – West (by White, Black, Hispanic) (Box 7)
      - Political Newspaper Clippings (Box 7)
      - Plot of Response Rates (Box 7)
      - Questionnaire Map (Box 7)
      - RIC Membership/ENS (Box 8)
      - VNS (Box 8)
      - Washington CD-5 Vertical Exit Poll (Box 8)
    - 1998
      - Absentees (Box 8)
      - America at the Polls (Box 8)
      - CBS/ CNN (Box 8)
      - New York Democratic Primary Poll (Box 8)
      - Polling (Box 8)
      - System Notes (Box 8)
      - VNS National Exit Poll (Box 8)
      - Voting and Registration in the Election of November 1998 (Box 8)
    - 2002
      - California Data (Box 8)
      - CNN Research and Editorial Guide (Box 8)
      - Decision Screen (Box 8)
      - Election Preview (Box 8)
      - Exit Poll Data (Box 8)
      - Final Election Analysis (Box 8)
      - General Election Manual (Box 8)
      - NCPP review of Election Polls (Box 8)
      - Precinct Election Design (Box 8)
      - VNS Vote Analysis Handbook (Box 8)
      - VNS State Research Reports (3 folders) (Box 8)
      - Voting and Registration in the Election of November 2002 (Box 8)
      - ESI – Cuyahoga County Exit Poll (Box 8)
      - NY Election Machines (Box 8)
  - Subseries C: U.S. off year Elections, 1965-2003
    - New York & New Jersey, 1965 (Box 8)
    - 1967
      - CBS News Coverage of the Kentucky Gubernatorial Election (Box 8)
      - Election Poll Survey in Kentucky, Philadelphia, and Cleveland (3 folders) (Box 8)
      - Kentucky Election Model (Box 8)
      - Kentucky Election Program (Box 8)
      - Kentucky Governor Statistical Methods (Box 8)
      - Kentucky Gubernatorial Election (Box 8)
      - Outline of Kentucky Model – Governor’s Race (Box 8)
    - New York Municipal Election, 1969 (Box 8)
    - New Jersey Exit Polls, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Chicago Democratic Primary Poll, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Kentucky, 1988 (Box 8)
    - 1989
      - Chicago Election Poll (Box 8)
      - Election Clippings (Box 8)
      - NYC/ New Jersey Elections (Box 8)
    - 1991
      - Old Chicago Polls/Primary (Box 8)
      - Louisiana Election (Box 8)
    - New York/ New Jersey Election, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Virginia/ New Jersey/New York City, 1997 (Box 8)
    - 2001
      - Election (2 folders) (Box 8)
      - Election (Box 9)
      - New Jersey Exit Poll (Box 9)
      - New York City Primary (Box 9)
      - California Governor Recall (Box 9)
    - 2003
      - California Recall (3 folders) (Box 9)
      - KY/ MS Election Questionnaires (Box 9)
      - NEP – CA Recall (Box 9)
      - NEP – KY/ MS (Box 9)
  - Subseries D: Foreign Elections, 1983-2006
    - Azerbaijan Contracts (2 folders), 2005 (Box 9)
    - Britain
      - The 1992 British Elections: The Failure of the Polls (Box 9)
      - British Elections/Pollsters, 1983, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
    - China Poll, 1989 (Box 9)
    - France, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Grenada, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Japan ese Exit Poll Article, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Mexico
      - 1983, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
      - Exit Poll Article Clippings, 1988 (Box 9)
      - 1993 (Box 9)
      - Belden Mexico Poll, 1994 (Box 9)
      - Documentation, Methodology, Etc. (Box 9)
      - Exit Poll, 1994 (Box 9)
      - Exit Poll Articles, 1994 (Box 9)
      - Exit Poll, 1994 (Box 9)
      - Election results, 1994 (Box 9)
      - Exit Poll, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Computations, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Elections, 1999-2000 (Box 9)
      - Consultant, 2000 (Box 9)
      - 2000 (Box 9)
      - Television Coverage, 2000 (Box 9)
      - Exit Poll, 2004 (Box 9)
      - 2003 (Box 9)
      - Press, 2006 (Box 9)
    - Pakistan Demographic Data, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Peru, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Philippines
      - Plissner, 1986 (Box 9)
      - Philippine Election, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
      - NAMFREL, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Puerto Rico, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Romania: Accurate Forecasts & Projections Jointly Produced by IRSOP & INFAS in the Romanian Presidential & Parliamentary Elections, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Russia
      - The Adventures of Murray & Warren in Moscow Week 1, 1993 (Box 9)
      - CESSI, 1993 (Box 9)
      - Correspondence with Russian Pollsters, 1993 (Box 9)
      - December, 1993 (Box 10)
      - December Storage, 1993 (Box 10)
      - Institute for Comparative and Social Research, 1993 (Box 10)
      - Moscow referendum, 1993 (Box 10)
      - Russia n Exit Polls and Articles, 1993 (Box 10)
      - Russia n Referendum, 1993 (Box 10)
      - Vote Data/Samples, 1993 (Box 10)
      - VRS Exit Poll, 1993 (Box 10)
      - Russia n Exit Polls, 1994 (Box 10)
      - Russia (3 folders), 1996 (Box 10)
      - Russia Exit Poll, 1996 (Box 10)
      - News Stories on Russia n Election, 1996 July 7 (Box 10)
      - Russia Presidential Run-off Exit Poll, 1996 (Box 10)
      - Duma Exit Poll, 1999 (Box 10)
      - Russia Duma, 2000 (Box 10)
      - Duma Exit Poll, 2003 (Box 10)
      - Russia Duma, 2003 (Box 10)
    - South Africa, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Sri Lanka
      - 1995 (Box 10)
      - 1994,1996 (Box 10)
      - The Sri Lankan Voter & the April 2004 Elections (Box 10)
    - Taiwan: Exit Poll and Results, 2000, 2004 (Box 10)
    - Ukraine: Exit Polls in Foreign Elections, 2005 (Box 10)
- Series II: Public Opinion and Data Gathering, undated, 1942-2005
  - Subseries A: Poll and Survey Articles and Methodology, undated, 1942-2001
    - AAPOR Abstract: “Methods and Standards a Challenge for Change,”, 1989 (Box 10)
    - AAPOR Code of Professional Ethics and Practices, undated (Box 10)
    - AAPOR Conference on polls, 1983 (Box 10)
    - AAPOR Plenary, 1981 (Box 10)
    - AAPOR Publications on Surveys, 1989-1991 (Box 10)
    - AAPOR: The Obligations of the 1950 Pollster to the 1984 Historian, undated (Box 10)
    - Articles about polls, 1984, 1985, 1988 (Box 10)
    - ASA: What is a Survey?, 1980 (Box 10)
    - A Short History of Exit Polling (Box 10)
    - A study in Response Errors in Expenditure Data from Household Surveys, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Bad Press – Exit Polls, 1980, 1982, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Bad Press – Exit Polls, 1983, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Bandwagon – A Review of the Literature, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Bandwagon – A Review of the Literature, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Bureau of the Census, 1966-1976 (Box 10)
    - Bureau of the Census Articles, 1942-1943, 1957, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Case Studies for National Council on Public Polls, 1979 (Box 11)
    - CASRO, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Common Objectives in Pre-Election Polling, 2000 (Box 11)
    - Commentary on “All the Polls Show…”, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Developing and Using Questionnaires, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Do Polls Effect Voting?, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Effects of Interviewing Designated Household Respondents in a Household Survey, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Esomar – Guide to Public Opinion Polls, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Estimation on Multivariate Approach, 1965 (Box 11)
    - E/S Unit Background, 1984, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Exit Polls, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Exit Polls and the Latino Voter, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Exit Polls and Voter Turnout in California, 1980, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Exit Poll Design Effects, 2003 (Box 11)
    - Exit Poll Trends, 1984-1985, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Exit Poll Research, 1986, 1990, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Experimental Study to Increase Exit Poll Response Rates and Reduce Survey Error, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Fanto Interviews with William Gammel, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Focus Groups, 1992, 1995-1996, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Gallup Conference, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Harris Interactive Online Survey, 1998-2000 (Box 11)
    - Hispanics Poll Paper, 1984 (Box 11)
    - “How to Judge a Poll” by Joseph T. Klapper, 1980 (Box 11)
    - How to treat non-response in marketing intelligence surveys, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Insight – Of Polls and Pols and Politics, 1988 (Box 11)
    - International Code of Practice for the Publishing of Public Opinion Results, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Internet Polling, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Interviewer’s Manual, Survey Research Center, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Introduction to Survey Design, undated (Box 11)
    - Journalist’s Guide to the Publishing of Opinion Survey Results, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Manipulating Polls, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Methodology for Survey Design in Developing Countries, 1983 (Box 11)
    - The Nation, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Newsroom Guide to Polls and Surveys, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Non-response in Exit Polls: A Comprehensive Analysis, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Off the Bandwagon: Some reflections on the influence of perceived public opinion, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Opinión Profesional, undated (Box 11)
    - Polls and Scandal, From Nixon to Clinton, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Political Quarterly Articles on Polling, 1984-1986 (Box 11)
    - Polling, 1977-1980 (Box 11)
    - Polling Goals, 1979, 1983-1985, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
    - Polling Papers, 1984, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Polling Review Board – NCPP, 2000-2001 (Box 11)
    - Pollsters, 1997-1999 (Box 11)
    - 1980 Pre-Election Polls: A Review of the Disparate Methods and Results, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Pseudo Opinion, 1994, 1996-1998 (Box 11)
    - Pseudo-Poll, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Public Opinion Polling by Nancy Josephson, undated (Box 11)
    - Refusal Rates, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Report on Refusal rates in CBS News/ NY Times Polls, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Research on Election Day Exit Polls, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Response Errors in Collection of Expenditures Data by Household Interviews: An Experimental Study, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Response Rates, 1995 (Box 11)
    - Ross Perot, 1993 (Box 11)
    - Ross Perot’s Special Interest Referendum (2 Folders), 1993 (Box 11)
    - Stratified Telephone Survey Designs, 1992 (Box 12)
    - Survey Methods of the Gallup Poll, 1965 (Box 12)
    - Survey USA, 2003 (Box 12)
    - Telephone Survey Methodology Conference, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Telephone Survey Papers, 1972, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
    - U.S. & Canada Census Concepts/World Industry, 1961 (Box 12)
    - Unidentified Articles and Papers on Polls and Surveys (2 Folders), undated (Box 12)
    - Voter Research and Surveys, 1972, 1993, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
    - WAPOR – The Freedom to Publish Opinion Polls, 1997-1998 (Box 12)
    - Web Polling, 2001 (Box 12)
    - Wimps No More: Guidance for Allocating Undecideds In Pre-Election Polls, 1993 (Box 12)
  - Subseries B: Sampling, 1961-2004
    - Census files PPS without replacement, 1961 (Box 12)
    - Debate with Humphrey Taylor, 2004 (Box 12)
    - Dollar-Unit Sampling in Auditing, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Friedrich Tennstädt, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Genesys (2 Folders), 1993 (Box 12)
    - Observations on “Outliers”, 1961 (Box 12)
    - Research into Half-day Sampling, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Sample Allocation for Stratified Telephone Sample Designs, 1992 (Box 12)
    - Sampling Applications in Censuses of Population & Housing, 1965 (Box 12)
    - Sampling Error Article, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Sampling Rare Populations: An Alternative Method, undated (Box 12)
    - Survey Sampling, Inc., 1993 (Box 12)
    - Telephone Sampling, 1970, 1982-1985, 1990-1993 (Box 12)
    - Unidentified Articles on Sampling, undated (Box 12)
    - VPA Sampling, 1967, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Subseries C: Statistics, 1955-2005
    - Apportionment Methods…, 1992 (Box 12)
    - Comments & Revised Comments on 2001: Statistical Stratifications for Estimating Election Outcomes (Box 12)
    - Contributions to Statistics, 1963 (Box 12)
    - “A Conversation with Joseph Waksberg, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Litigation and Statistics, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Papers and Articles on Statistics, 1955, 1972, 1981, 2005 (Box 12)
    - Questions/Answers from the Survey Statistician, 1978-1994 (Box 12)
    - “Scaling & Test Theory”, 1961 (Box 12)
    - Standards for Discussion and Presentation of Errors in Data, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Statistical Standards and Practices, 1965 (Box 12)
    - Statistics, 1965, 1972, 1977, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Statistics, 2001 (Box 12)
- Series III: Election Projections, undated, 1952-2005
  - Subseries A: Models and Methodology, undated, 1952-2005
    - ASA – Halpern – ABC, 1990-1991 (Box 12)
    - ASA – Some Approaches to Election Night Forecasting in Australia, 1987 (Box 12)
    - CBS Election Night Estimation, 1972, 1985, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
    - CBS Prediction Model, 1964, 1966 (Box 12)
    - CBS Probability Models, 1967 (Box 12)
    - Computations for CNN System, 2002 (Box 12)
    - Election Estimation from Incomplete Sample Data, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Election Forecasting JASA, 2005 (Box 12)
    - Election Night Forecasting, undated (Box 12)
    - Election Projection Seminar, undated (Box 12)
    - Election Projection Model, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Estimating and Analyzing Election Returns, 1968 (Box 12)
    - Estimation of the Error of Synthetic Estimates, 1973, 1988 (Box 12)
    - History of CBS Prediction, undated (Box 12)
    - How UNIVAC Predicted the Election for CBS-TV, 1952 (Box 12)
    - Methodology for CBS News Election Analysis, undated (Box 12)
    - Articles on Computers and Election Prediction, 1964, 1969, 1992 (Box 12)
    - Probability Models for Estimating Election Night Returns – CBS News, 1967 (Box 12)
    - Probability Models for Estimating Election Night Returns (2 Folders), 1967 (Box 12)
    - Psephological Analysis: A Report to the American Broadcasting Company, undated (Box 12)
    - Public opinion Surveys & Electoral Forecasting in Great Britain, 1985 (Box 12)
    - A Sampling Procedure for Election Night Prediction, 1967 (Box 12)
    - Types of Precinct Data Which Would be Useful for Elections Night Analysis…, 1967 (Box 12)
    - VNS Log, 1997, 2001, 2003-2004 (Box 13)
    - VNS – Statistical Specifications for Estimating Election Outcomes, 2001 (Box 13)
    - VNS – Statistical Specifications for Estimating Election Outcomes, 2002 (Box 13)
    - VNA Model (2 Folders), 1968 (Box 13)
    - VPA Seminar I (2 Folders), 1964 (Box 13)
    - VPA Seminar II (2 Folders), 1964 (Box 13)
    - XL. County System, undated (Box 13)
  - Subseries B: T.V. Coverage and the Effect on Voters, 1961-2002
    - A Challenge for Campaign ’92, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Affect of the Media on Western Voting, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Analysis of the Effect of Election Night Predictions on Voting Behavior, 1965 (Box 13)
    - A Report on a Study for Estimating Non-Voters as a Result of Election Projections – Westat, Inc., 1984 (Box 13)
    - Ballots & Broadcasts: Exposure to Election Broadcasts and Terminal Voting Decisions (3 folders), 1965 (Box 13)
    - CNN Political Questions and Answers, 2001 (Box 13)
    - A Commentary on “Exposure to Election Broadcasts and Terminal Voting Decisions (2 Folders), 1965 (Box 13)
    - The “Early” Election Projection Controversy, undated (Box 13)
    - Early Election Projections in 1984: How Oregon Voters Deplored but Ignored Them, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Early Projections, 2000 (Box 13)
    - The Effects of Election Day Broadcasts on Voting: Kittitas County, Washington, 1980 (Box 13)
    - “Election Night Estimation”, 2001 (Box 13)
    - Election Night Reporting and Voter Turnout, undated (Box 13)
    - Election Projections: Hypocracy by the Washington Post and New York Times, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Exposure to Election Broadcasts and Terminal Voting Decisions (2 Folders), 1965 (Box 13)
    - Exit Poll Controversy (2 Folders), 1985-1986 (Box 13)
    - The Gallup Organization/Office of Social Research Study, 1967, 1990 (Box 13)
    - History of Election Night Coverage and Projections, 2002 (Box 13)
    - The Impact of Expectations and Election Day Perceptions on Voting Behavior (2 Folders), 1965 (Box 13)
    - The Influence of Television Election Broadcasts in a Close Election, 1969 (Box 13)
    - Articles on Election Projections (2 Folders), undated (Box 13)
    - NBC Illustrative Example of the Types of Information Available on a Network Television Program, 1961 (Box 13)
    - NBC News Summary of Election Night Review, 2001 (Box 13)
    - NCPP – On Being Elite and In-the-know on Election Day!, 1997 (Box 13)
    - Network “Early Calls” of Elections: An Analysis of the Legality of the Proposals, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Nexus – Transcripts, 1984, 1988, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Polls & Television News/Probable Electorate Weighting Procedure, undated (Box 13)
    - Projection Effects/BSSR (2 Folders), 1984 (Box 13)
    - Public Reaction to the Use of Computers in Television Coverage of 1966 Election Returns, 1967 (Box 14)
    - Reflections on Televisions Roles in American Presidential Elections, 1990 (Box 14)
    - Report on a Study for Estimating Non-Voters as a Result of Election Projections, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Scooping the Voters? The Consequences of Networks’ Early Call of the 1980 Presidential Race, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Study: If There Were No Projections on Election Night, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Television’s Performance on Election Night 2000 – CNN (Box 14)
    - Tuning & Turning Out, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Voting for Democracy ( 2 Folders), undated (Box 14)
- Series IV: Litigation, 1966-2005
  - Affidavit – Anne Reingold, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Affidavit – Patrice LoCicero, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Amerivest Financial Group, Inc., 1996-1997 (Box 14)
  - Analysis of the Request of William Ling, CPA, 1998 (Box 14)
  - AP, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Capital Defender Office, 2003-2004 (Box 14)
  - Clean-up ’84 v. Walter C. Heinrich, undated (Box 14)
  - The Daily Herald Company v. Ralph Munro (3 Folders), 1984 (Box 14)
  - Daily Herald Exit Poll Articles, undated (Box 14)
  - Dinnerstein – Capital Defender, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Edward Labaton, 1997 (Box 14)
  - ENS, 1994 (Box 14)
  - Exit Poll – Case in FL/ GA –Information for Testimony, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Insured Energy Drilling Program v. Heritage Resources Inc., 1992 (Box 14)
  - International News Service v. Associated Press, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Libya n Producers’ Agreement, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Lizzie Grubman, 2001 (Box 14)
  - LPA Arbitration, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Marshall B. Grossman vs. Playboy Clubs International, Inc., 1966 (Box 14)
  - NBC v. Cleland ( Georgia Exit Polling Case), 1988 (Box 14)
  - NES Agreement, 1967, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Nevada Election, 2004 (Box 14)
  - New Mexico Election, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Ohio Election, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Ohio & Hawaii State Official Letters, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Old Stock Litigation (3 Folders), 1994, 1996-2000 (Box 14)
  - Oxford Oil & Gas, Inc., 1996-1997 (Box 14)
  - The People of New York v. Kenneth Boss, Sean Carroll, Edward McMellon, and Richard Murphy, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Proposed Stipulated Facts Submitted by Hunt, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Rice v. Paladin Enterprises, Inc., 1997 (Box 14)
  - Ronnell Wilson Case – New York, 2003-2004 (Box 14)
  - S.E.C. Case, 1998 (Box 14)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission v. Whitworth Energy Resources, Ltd., 1998 (Box 14)
  - Starbucks v. Charbucks, 2005 (Box 15)
  - State of Utah v. Donald L. Evans, 2001 (Box 15)
  - United States District Court (2 Folders), 1997 (Box 15)
  - “United States District Court for the District of South Carolina, Columbia Division”, 1998 (Box 15)
  - Washington Law Suit ( 2 Folders), 1984 (Box 15)
- Series V: Legislative Materials, 1967-2006
  - Anne Reingold, Martin Plissner, Howard F. Jaeckel, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Before the Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Before the Subcommittee on Elections, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Committee on Energy and Commerce, 2001 (Box 15)
  - Committee on Open Government, 1987, 1992-1993 (Box 15)
  - Committee on Open Government, 1991-1993 (Box 15)
  - Congressional Hearings, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Congressional Hearing, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Conyers & Others, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Ed Joyce, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Evaluation of Statistical Methods Used in Obtaining Broadcast Ratings Report of the Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1961 (Box 15)
  - Exit Polls Laws, 1984,1988, 2004, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Hearing Before the Committee on Energy and Commerce, 2001 (Box 15)
  - Hearings before the Subcommittee on Communications of the Committee on Commerce (2 Folders), 1967 (Box 15)
  - Hearings before the Subcommittee on Library and Memorials of the Committee on House Administration, 1972 (Box 15)
  - Hearings held Before the Task Force on Elections and the Subcommittee on Telecommunications, Consumer Protection, and Finance, 1981-1982 (Box 15)
  - House Briefing Notes, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Joint Hearing Before the Committee on House Administration and the Subcommittee on Telecommunications, Consumer Protection, and Finance (2 Folders), 1981 (Box 15)
  - Joint Hearing Before the Subcommittee on Telecommunications, Consumer Protection, and Finance and the Task Force on Elections, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Joint Hearing on “Election results and Early Voting”, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Larry Fraiberg, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Newspapers Opposition to Legislation’s Intent to Restrict T.V. Exit Polling, 1984 (Box 15)
  - NY Committee on Open Government, 1993 (Box 15)
  - Papers and Articles regarding Congressional Hearings, 1967, 1981, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Projection Controversy, 1984 (Box 15)
  - The Regulation of Early Projections: Legal Foundations, undated (Box 15)
  - Report by the Committee of House Administration on Single Poll Closing Time for Presidential General Elections in the Continental United States, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Some Remarks on the Report of the Technical Committee on Broadcast Ratings…, undated (Box 16)
  - Statement by Frank Stanton and Frank Jordan, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Senate Ques, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Testimony from Congressional Hearings, 1967, 1982, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Testimony of California Secretary of State, 1981, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Washington State Legislature Prohibition of Exit Polling, 1983 (Box 16)
- Series VI: Surveys and Studies, 1944-2006
  - Ann Selzer, 1996 (Box 16)
  - AVON, 1992 (Box 16)
  - CBS News Poll: Grenada After the Fighting, 1983 (Box 16)
  - CBS News Study: Generations Apart, 1969 (Box 16)
  - CBS News Telephone Survey, 1969 (Box 16)
  - CBS/NY Times Poll: Attitudes Towards NYC Financial Problems, 1975 (Box 16)
  - Celebrating the Four-Hundredth Anniversary of the First Survey research in America, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Columbia University Department of Psychiatry and School of Public Health Study, 1995 (Box 16)
  - Diallo (2 Folders), 1999 (Box 16)